http://www.mahlkoenig.de/pages/privacy-policy

Our webshops are currently shipping within the US and Germany, only.
Our webshops are currently shipping within the US and Germany, only.
Privacy Policy
We, the Hemro Manufactoring Germany GmbH (Hemro/we) are pleased about your visit to our website and your interest in Hemro. In the following provisions we inform you about the type, scope and purposes of the collection and use of your personal data on this website. Personal data is any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person. This includes in particular your name, your address and your e-mail address.
1.    Data processing to enable the use of the websiteWith each access to contents of our website, connection data is transmitted to our web server. This connection data includes:•    the IP address (Internet Protocol address) of the respective users,•    the date and time of the request, •    the referrer-URL,•    device numbers such as UDID (Unique Device Identifier) and comparable device numbers, device information (e.g. device type) and•    the browser type / the browser version.This connection data are not used to draw conclusions about the user’s identity or are combined with data from other data sources, but serve to provide the website. The legal basis for the processing of your data is Art. 6 para. 1 sentence 1 lit. f GDPR. After 7 days at the latest, the connection data will be anonymised by shortening the IP address at domain level.
2.    Processing of data on initiativeThe use of our website is usually possible without providing personal data. You are neither obliged to visit this website nor to provide any personal data. The provision of personal data is also not necessary for the conclusion of a contract. If you do not provide us with personal data, you may not be able to use individual functionalities or services of this website. Other than that there will be no consequences for you. We process your personal data when you use the following service offered by us:
2.1.    Dealer areaIf you register with us as a dealer and use the dealer area on our website, we will process your data for this purpose.The processing of your personal data is based on Art. 6 para. 1 sentence 1 lit. b GDPR.
2.2.    Contact formIf you contact us using the contact form provided, your details will be stored so that they can be used to process your request. To contact us, it is sufficient to enter your e-mail address. The additional voluntary information about your person serves only to personalize the contact for you.The legal basis for the processing of your data is generally based on Art. 6 para. 1 sentence 1 lit. f GDPR. Our legitimate interest then consists in answering your request. In the case of the implementation of (pre-)contractual measures, the legal basis is Art. 6 para. 1 sentence 1 lit. b GDPR. 2.3.    NewsletterIf you have expressly agreed, you will receive our newsletter. To receive our newsletter, it is sufficient to enter your e-mail address. The additional voluntary information about your person only serves to personalize the newsletter for you. For the registration to our newsletter we use the so-called double-opt-in procedure. This means that after your registration we will send you an e-mail to the given e-mail address in which we ask you to confirm that you wish to receive the newsletter. If you do not confirm your registration within 24 hours, your information will be blocked and automatically deleted after one month. Your personal data will be processed on the basis of your consent in accordance with Art. 6 para. 1 sentence 1 lit. a GDPR. You can revoke your consent at any time with effect for the future. Revocation of consent does not affect the lawfulness of the processing carried out on the basis of the consent until revocation. There is a link at the end of each newsletter to exercise the right of revocation. Alternatively, you can revoke your consent at any time, e.g. by sending an e-mail to marketing@hemrogroup.com. When you register for a newsletter, we will also store your IP address and the time of registration in order to comply with our legal documentation obligation. The legal basis for data processing in this case is Art. 6 para. 1 sentence 1 lit. c GDPR.
3.    Data processing for the demand-oriented design of the websiteTo make the use of our website as pleasant as possible for you, we use so-called web tracking systems. For this purpose, cookies are generally used, i.e. small text files that are sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. This enables us to recognize the end device used by you when you visit the website repeatedly. Most browsers are set in such a way that cookies are automatically accepted. You can deactivate the storage of cookies in your browser and have the option of deleting them from your hard drive at any time. However, you can also use your browser to prevent the setting of certain cookies only (e.g. cookies from third parties), for example if you wish to prevent web tracking. You can find more information on this in the help function of your browser.  We would further like to point out that you can also install a plugin in your browser to protect your privacy, which offers the possibility of preventing tracking - e.g. AdBlock, Ghostery or NoScript (please refer to the data protection information of the respective plugin provider).  Finally, please note that if you disable cookies, you may not be able to use all the features or services of this website to their full extent.
3.1.    Cookie consent with the cookie consent toolIn order to be able to administer your consent to the use of tracking tools, we use the cookie consent tool "Free GDPR + Cookie Management" from the provider iSenseLabs. In this context, in addition to the connection data, the granting or refusal of your consent or the revocation of a consent is processed. In order to be able to make the corresponding allocation, the cookie consent tool also sets a cookie in your browser. If you wish to revoke these settings, simply delete the cookies in your browser (see also section 3). Further information on data protection is available at: https://gdpr.apps.isenselabs.com/pages/privacy_policy.The cookie consent tool is used to obtain the legally required consent for the use of cookies. The legal basis for this is Art. 6 para. 1 sentence 1 lit. c GDPR.
3.2.    YouTubeOur website uses plugins from the Google operated YouTube page. If you visit one of our websites equipped with a YouTube plugin and actively click on the corresponding field, a connection to the servers of YouTube is established. This tells the YouTube server which of our websites you have visited. If you are logged in to your YouTube account, you allow YouTube to assign your surfing behavior directly to your personal profile. You can prevent this by logging out of your YouTube account. YouTube is used in the interest of an attractive presentation of our online offers. This represents a legitimate interest in the sense of Art. 6 para. 1 sentence 1 lit. f GDPR.Further information on the handling of user data can be found in the YouTube privacy policy at: https://www.google.de/intl/de/policies/privacy.
3.3.    Google AnalyticsOur website uses the tracking tool "Google Analytics". This is a service provided by Google Ireland Limited, a company incorporated and regulated under Irish law with its registered office at Gordon House, Barrow Street, Dublin 4, Ireland (Google). This tracking tool helps us to make the website more interesting for you and to improve the user experience. In doing so, data on the use of our website is stored in pseudonymous user profiles. Cookies can also be used for this purpose. In addition, data from various devices, sessions and interactions can be linked to a so-called "user ID". The generated information are usually transferred to a Google server in the USA and stored there. We would like to point out that on our website Google Analytics has been extended by the "anonymizeIp" function. This means that your IP address is first shortened by Google within member states of the European Union or in other contracting states of the Agreement on the European Economic Area and only then transferred to a Google server in the USA. Google has submitted to the EU-US privacy shield, https://www.privacyshield.gov/EU-US-Framework. On our behalf, Google will use the information received to evaluate your use of our website, to compile reports on website activity and to provide us with further services related to website and internet usage. The pseudonymised user profiles will not be merged with personal data about the bearer of the pseudonym without a separately granted consent.Further information about Google Analytics can be found at:https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/2790010?hl=de  The legal basis for the processing of your data is your consent in accordance with Art. 6 para. 1 sentence 1 lit. a GDPR. You give your corresponding consent via our cookie banner. As described above under section 3, you can prevent the use of cookies by adjusting your browser software settings accordingly or object to them for the future. You can also prevent the collection of data generated by the cookie and relating to your use of our website by clicking on the following link: (http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=de) to download and install the available browser plugin. In addition, you can also prevent Google Analytics from collecting the data by clicking on the following text: Google Tag Manager / deactivate Google Analytics. This will set a so-called opt-out cookie, which will prevent the future collection of your data when you visit our website. If you use different devices, you must carry out the above-mentioned measures on each end device. Please note, however, that if you delete your cookies, the opt-out cookie will also be deleted and may have to be reactivated by you.
4.    Social media presence4.1.    Links to social networksOur website contains links to social networks (Facebook, Twitter, Instagram and YouTube). These websites are operated exclusively by third parties. If you follow the links, the respective provider may process personal data about you. Please note the data protection information of the provider in this regard.
4.2.    Data processing by Hemro and legal basisOur social media sites (Facebook, Twitter, Instagram and YouTube) serve the purpose of informing you about Hemro and new developments, services and products from us. Depending on the offer of the respective providers, you have the possibility of different interaction (comments, recommendations etc.) e.g. in connection with our social media presence. The interaction of the users is an important criterion for us in order to carry out targeted marketing. For example, we can determine which articles are read preferentially. We therefore also use the statistics determined by the providers in this regard for our own purposes. Insofar as we process personal data of users in this context, the legal basis for this is Art. 6 para. 1 sentence 1 lit. f GDPR. Our legitimate interest then consists in particular in targeted information / advertising. The providers will inform you separately about the legal basis on which they process your data for their own purposes.
4.3.    Joint controllersIn some cases we are jointly responsible (joint controllers) with the social media providers for processing your personal data. In this case you can assert your rights (see section 9) generally either against us or against the social media provider. However, the social media provider is the first point of contact. We have entered into a joint controller agreement with Facebook Inc, 1 Hacker Way, Menlo Park, California 94025, USA (Facebook) regarding the processing of personal data. This agreement applies with regard to the processing of so-called "insights data". These are page statistics, especially regarding the interactions of Facebook users. Details of the insights data can be found here: https://www.facebook.com/business/pages/manage#page_insights. Our agreement with Facebook can be viewed at the following link: www.facebook.com/legal/terms/page_controller_addendum. With regard to the storage period of the data processed by us for our own purposes, we refer you to our explanations under section 7. In addition, please note the data protection regulations of the respective social media provider.
5.    Data transferWe will only transfer your personal data to third parties or other recipients if this is necessary for the provision of services, if you have given your consent, if there is a legal obligation to do so or if the transfer of data is permitted on another legal basis. For example, data is passed on to technical service providers or - in the case of a company transaction - to interested parties/buyers etc. We also use the services of the service provider Shopify International Limited, Victoria Buildings, 2nd floor, 1-2 Haddington Road, Dublin 4, D04 XN32, Ireland (Shopify), for the purpose of hosting our website and in connection with the cookie consent tool. To the extent necessary, we have entered into data processing agreements with the recipients of your data in accordance with Art. 28 GDPR.
6.    Data transfer to countries outside the EUWhere necessary for our purposes, we will also transfer your data to recipients outside the EU, if it is ensured that the recipient of the data guarantees an adequate level of data protection and that there are no other legitimate interests against the data transfer. As part of the use of Shopify (see section 5), personal data may be transferred to Shopify Inc. in Canada or the USA. In the event that data is transferred to Shopify Inc. in Canada, an adequacy finding by the European Commission ensures an adequate level of data protection. Shopify Inc. companies in the USA are "privacy shield" certified. For further information on Shopify's privacy policy, please visit the following website: https://www.shopify.de/legal/datenschutz.
7.    Duration for which personal data are stored / criteria for determining the durationYour personal data will be stored by us for as long as it is necessary for the aforementioned purposes of processing, in the event of an objection no compelling reasons worthy of protection oppose Hemro or in the event of a revocation no other legal basis for data processing exists. In certain cases, e.g. if there is a legal obligation to retain data, your personal data will not be deleted immediately, but blocked initially. Thus, the retention period for messages via the contact form with a business content can be ten years.
8.    Security measures to protect your personal dataWe protect your data against unauthorized access, loss or destruction by technical and organizational measures. Our security measures are continuously improved in line with technological developments. Our employees and all persons involved in data processing are obliged to comply with data protection laws and to handle personal data confidentially. Our employees are trained accordingly.To protect your personal data on this website, we use a secure online transmission procedure, the so-called "Secure Socket Layer" (SSL) transmission. You can recognize this by the fact that a closed padlock symbol is displayed on the address https://. By clicking on the symbol you will receive information about the SSL certificate used. The display of the symbol depends on the browser version you are using. The SSL encryption guarantees the encrypted and complete transmission of your data.
9.    Your rights Within the framework of the legal requirements, you have a fundamental claim against Hemro for•    confirmation as to whether personal data concerning you is processed by Hemro,•    information about these data and the circumstances of the processing,•    correction, if these data are incorrect, •    deletion, unless the processing is not justified and there is no (longer an) obligation to keep the data,•    restriction of processing in special cases determined by law, •    objection in case of data processing on the basis of Art. 6 para. 1 sentence 1 lit. f GDPR and•    transmission of your personal data – if you have provided it – to you or a third party in a structured, common and machine-readable format.Insofar as the processing of your personal data is based on your consent, you have the right to revoke this consent at any time, with the consequence that the processing of your personal data will become inadmissible for the future. However, this does not affect the lawfulness of the processing carried out on the basis of the consent up to the point of revocation. Please address your specific request in writing or by e-mail to our data protection officer, clearly identifying yourself:
krupna LEGAL
Data protection officer
Am Sandtorkai 77
20457 Hamburg
E-Mail: office@krupna.legalInsofar as we process your data in joint controllership with third parties within the meaning of Art. 26 GDPR, the third party is centrally responsible for the exercise of all rights of the persons concerned. However, you are at liberty to assert your rights against us as well.Finally, we would like to draw your attention to your right of appeal to the supervisory authority.
10.    No automated individual decisionWe do not use your personal data for automated individual decisions.
11.    Amendment of the privacy policyNew legal requirements, business decisions or technical developments may require changes to our privacy policy. The privacy policy will then be adjusted accordingly. You will always find the latest version on our website.
Mahlkönig
Products
Service
News & Events
Newsletter
About Us
Hemro Group
Legal Notice
Copyright 2020 of Hemro Manufacturing Germany GmbH. All Rights Reserved
Added to your cart:
Subtotal
I have read and agree to the terms and conditions and to the cancellation policy. (Click here to read)
* Please agree to the terms and conditions before making a purchase!
EN
DE
EN
DE
